Francis D. Donovan Papers
© 2011 University of Connecticut
- Series VI: Photographic materials, undated, 1829-1997
  - Subseries A: Prints, undated, 1829-1997
    - Sub-subseries 1: Stations, undated, 1858-1997
      - Alton Bay, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1906 (Box 14:, Folder 1478)
      - Alton Bay, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1880 (Box 14:, Folder 1479)
      - Ames, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 14:, Folder 1480)
      - Anderson, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 14:, Folder 1481)
      - Andover, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 14:, Folder 1482)
      - Andover, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 14:, Folder 1483)
      - Antrim, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 14:, Folder 1484)
      - Ashland, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 15:, Folder 1485)
      - Auburn, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1486)
      - Bagley, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1487)
      - Barnstead, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1488)
      - Barrington, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1489)
      - Bedford, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1490)
      - Belknap Point, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1491)
      - Belknap Point, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1961 (Box 15:, Folder 1492)
      - Belknap Point, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1966 (Box 15:, Folder 1493)
      - Belknap Point, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1966 (Box 15:, Folder 1494)
      - Belknap Point, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1966 (Box 15:, Folder 1495)
      - Belmont, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1496)
      - Bennington, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1940 (Box 15:, Folder 1497)
      - Bennington, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 15:, Folder 1498)
      - Berlin, New Hampshire, Grand Trunk Railroad station, 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 1499)
      - Berlin, New Hampshire, Grand Trunk Railroad station, 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 1500)
      - Blodgett, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1501)
      - Boscawen, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1502)
      - Bow Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1503)
      - Bradford, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1963 (Box 15:, Folder 1504)
      - Bradford, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 15:, Folder 1505)
      - Bretton Woods, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1933 (Box 15:, Folder 1506)
      - Brookline, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1507)
      - Canaan, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1508)
      - Candia, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1509)
      - Canterbury, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1510)
      - Center Barnstead, New Hampshire, Suncook Valley Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1511)
      - Charlestown, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 15:, Folder 1512)
      - Charlestown, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1513)
      - Chichester, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1514)
      - Claremont Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1971 (Box 15:, Folder 1515)
      - Claremont Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1516)
      - Claremont Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1961 (Box 15:, Folder 1517)
      - Contoocook, New Hampshire, Claremont & Concord Railroad station, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 1518)
      - Converse, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1519)
      - Coos Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1520)
      - Derry, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1963 (Box 15:, Folder 1521)
      - Derry, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1522)
      - Dimond, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1523)
      - Dover, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1524)
      - Durham, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1525)
      - East Candia, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1526)
      - East Manchester, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1527)
      - East Side, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1528)
      - East Weare, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1529)
      - Enfield, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1530)
      - Epsom, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1531)
      - Everett, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1532)
      - Exeter, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1981 (Box 15:, Folder 1533)
      - Exeter, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1981 (Box 15:, Folder 1534)
      - Exeter, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1981 (Box 15:, Folder 1535)
      - Exeter, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1536)
      - Fabyan, New Hampshire, Maine Central Railroad station, 1964 (Box 15:, Folder 1537)
      - Fitzwilliam, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 1538)
      - Fitzwilliam, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 1539)
      - Forest Lake, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, circa 1934 (Box 15:, Folder 1540)
      - Franklin Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1541)
      - Franklin Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1542)
      - Gale, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1543)
      - Garrison, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 1544)
      - Gerrish, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1545)
      - Gerrish, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 1546)
      - Gerrish, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 1547)
      - Gilford, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1548)
      - Glendale, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1549)
      - Glen & Jackson, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1983 (Box 15:, Folder 1550)
      - Goff's Falls, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1551)
      - Goff's Town, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1552)
      - Goff's Town, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1553)
      - Gonic, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1554)
      - Gorham, New Hampshire, Grand Trunk Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1555)
      - Gorham, New Hampshire, Grand Trunk Railroad station, 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 1556)
      - Grafton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1557)
      - Grasmere, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1558)
      - Grasmere, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1559)
      - Great Falls, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1892 (Box 15:, Folder 1560)
      - Greenville, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1561)
      - Greystone, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1562)
      - Groveton, New Hampshire, Grand Trunk Railroad station, 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 1563)
      - Groveton, New Hampshire, Grand Trunk Railroad station, 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 1564)
      - Hampstead, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1565)
      - Hampton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 1566)
      - Hancock, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1567)
      - Harrisville, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1568)
      - Henniker Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1569)
      - Henniker Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1930 (Box 15:, Folder 1570)
      - Hollis, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1571)
      - Hollis, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1572)
      - Hollis Center, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1910 (Box 15:, Folder 1573)
      - Holton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1574)
      - Hooksett, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1575)
      - Hooksett, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1576)
      - Hubbard, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1577)
      - Hudson, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1578)
      - Intervale, New Hampshire, railroad station, 1976 (Box 15:, Folder 1579)
      - Intervale, New Hampshire, railroad station, 1976 (Box 15:, Folder 1580)
      - Joslin, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1581)
      - Keene, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1582)
      - Keewaydin, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1583)
      - Laconia, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 1584)
      - Lakeport, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 15:, Folder 1585)
      - Lake Shore Park, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1586)
      - Lake Sunapee, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1907 (Box 15:, Folder 1587)
      - Lake Sunapee, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 15:, Folder 1588)
      - Lisbon, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1589)
      - Lisbon, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1590)
      - Lisbon, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1970 (Box 16:, Folder 1591)
      - Littlefield, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1950 (Box 16:, Folder 1592)
      - Littleton-Bethlehem, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1593)
      - Londonderry, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1929 (Box 16:, Folder 1594)
      - Londonderry, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1595)
      - Madbury, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1596)
      - Madbury, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 16:, Folder 1597)
      - Manchester, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1598)
      - Manchester, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1599)
      - Maplewood, New Hampshire, Maine Central Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1600)
      - Marlboro, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, circa 1936 (Box 16:, Folder 1601)
      - Mascoma, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1602)
      - Mason, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1603)
      - Massabesic, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1604)
      - Mast Yard, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1605)
      - Meadowbrook, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1606)
      - Melvin, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1607)
      - Merrimack, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1608)
      - Milton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1905 (Box 16:, Folder 1609)
      - Moore's Crossing, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1610)
      - Mount Whittier, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 16:, Folder 1611)
      - Nashua, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1612)
      - Nashua, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1613)
      - Nashua, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, circa 1915 (Box 16:, Folder 1614)
      - Nashua, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1960 (Box 16:, Folder 1615)
      - Newbury, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1616)
      - Newmarket, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1981 (Box 16:, Folder 1617)
      - Newmarket, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1618)
      - Newport, New Hampshire, Claremont & Concord Railroad station, un1964dated (Box 16:, Folder 1619)
      - Newport Junction, New Hampshire, Maine Central Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1620)
      - North Charlestown, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 16:, Folder 1621)
      - North Conway, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1622)
      - North Hampton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1925 (Box 16:, Folder 1623)
      - North Hampton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1624)
      - North Hampton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1973 (Box 16:, Folder 1625)
      - North Hampton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1973 (Box 16:, Folder 1626)
      - Notchland, New Hampshire, Maine Central Railroad station, 1930 (Box 16:, Folder 1627)
      - Ossipee, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1628)
      - Ossipee, New Hampshire, railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1629)
      - Ossipee, New Hampshire, railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1630)
      - Parker's, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1631)
      - Penacook, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1632)
      - Peterboro, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1940 (Box 16:, Folder 1633)
      - Pickering, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1634)
      - Plymouth, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 16:, Folder 1635)
      - Portsmouth, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1929 (Box 16:, Folder 1636)
      - Potter Place, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1637)
      - Potter Place, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1997 (Box 16:, Folder 1638)
      - Potter Place, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1997 (Box 16:, Folder 1639)
      - Potter Place, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1997 (Box 16:, Folder 1640)
      - Potter Place, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1997 (Box 16:, Folder 1641)
      - Potter Place, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1997 (Box 16:, Folder 1642)
      - Potter Place, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1997 (Box 16:, Folder 1643)
      - Potter Place, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1997 (Box 16:, Folder 1644)
      - Pratt, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1645)
      - Raymond, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1646)
      - Reed's Ferry, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1647)
      - Rindgemere, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1648)
      - Riverdale, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1649)
      - Roby, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1650)
      - Rockingham Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1981 (Box 16:, Folder 1651)
      - Rockingham Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1981 (Box 16:, Folder 1652)
      - Rockingham Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1981 (Box 16:, Folder 1653)
      - Salem, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1654)
      - Sargent, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1655)
      - Scott's Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1656)
      - Severances, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1657)
      - Short Falls, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1658)
      - Smith's Point, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1659)
      - South Bennington, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1660)
      - South Charlestown, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1661)
      - South Nashua, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1662)
      - Springhaven, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1663)
      - State Line, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1664)
      - State Line, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1665)
      - Stratham, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1666)
      - Sunapee, New Hampshire, Claremont & Concord Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1667)
      - Suncook, New Hampshire, Suncook Valley Railroad station, 1935 (Box 16:, Folder 1668)
      - Swainboro, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1669)
      - Terrace Hill, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1670)
      - Thornton's Ferry, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1671)
      - Troy, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1963 (Box 16:, Folder 1672)
      - Troy, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1963 (Box 16:, Folder 1673)
      - Union, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1920 (Box 16:, Folder 1674)
      - Walpole, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1675)
      - Warner, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1676)
      - Waterloo, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1677)
      - Webb, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1678)
      - Webster Lake, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1679)
      - Webster Mills, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1680)
      - Webster Place, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1681)
      - Weir Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 16:, Folder 1685)
      - Weirs, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1977 (Box 16:, Folder 1682)
      - Weirs, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1971 (Box 16:, Folder 1683)
      - Weirs, New Hampshire, Boston, Concord & Montreal Railroad station, 1878 (Box 16:, Folder 1684)
      - Weirs, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1971 (Box 16:, Folder 1686)
      - Weirs, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1971 (Box 16:, Folder 1687)
      - Weirs Beach, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 17:, Folder 1688)
      - Wentworth, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1689)
      - West Alton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1690)
      - West Alton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 1691)
      - West Alton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 1692)
      - West Alton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 1693)
      - West Claremont, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1695)
      - West Deering, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1696)
      - West Epping, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1697)
      - West Manchester, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1698)
      - Westboro, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1694)
      - Whitefield, New Hampshire, Maine Central Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1699)
      - Whitefield, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1970 (Box 17:, Folder 1700)
      - Wilton, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 17:, Folder 1701)
      - Windham, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, circa 1935 (Box 17:, Folder 1702)
      - Windham, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1963 (Box 17:, Folder 1703)
      - Winnisquah, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 17:, Folder 1704)
      - Winnisquah, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1705)
      - Winnisquah, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1706)
      - Wolfoboro Junction, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1707)
      - Wolfboro, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1708)
      - Wolfboro, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1709)
      - Woodlands, New Hampshire, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1710)
      - Unidentified, New Hampshire, railroad station, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1711)
      - Demorest, New Jersey, Erie Railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1712)
      - Demorest, New Jersey, Erie Railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1713)
      - Demorest, New Jersey, Erie Railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1714)
      - Demorest, New Jersey, Erie Railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1715)
      - Demorest, New Jersey, Erie Railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1716)
      - Demorest, New Jersey, Erie Railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1717)
      - Englewood, New Jersey, Erie Railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1718)
      - Englewood, New Jersey, Erie Railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1719)
      - Hackensack, New Jersey, railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1720)
      - Hackensack, New Jersey, railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1721)
      - Hackensack, New Jersey, railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1722)
      - Tenafly, New Jersey, Erie Railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1723)
      - Tenafly, New Jersey, Erie Railroad station, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 1724)